Xu Peng (Linus)

16 Arran St • Seddon • VIC 3011

Phone (61) 0426-829324 • E-MAIL penxumelb@gmail.com • Website: https://linusmelb.github.io

.....

EDUCATION

The University of Melbourne

Bachelor of Science, Software Systems

National University of Singapore – 2017.07 - 2017.12

Exchange program, Computer Science

SUMMARY

Innovative tech mind with 3 years of experience working as a web developer. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, and managing databases. Valuable team member who has experience diagnosing problems and developing solutions. Talented programmer with unique ideas and a huge passion for learning new things.

SKILLS

Language: HTML5, CSS3, ES7, PHP, Python, C, Java, Haskell

Database: MySql, Sqlite

Front-end: Bootstrap 4, JQuery, Vue.js, D3.js, ElementUI

Back-end: Laravel, Codeigniter, Flask, Wordpress

Server: Nginx, Apache

Marketing Platform: MailChimp

RCS: Git

Others: Webpack, NPM, Mpvue

EXPERIENCE

Novatti Group Limited(ASX:NOV), Software developer & SEO developer 2018.07 – present

- Project link https://www.chinapayments.com
- Led, architected and participated in the design, testing and deployment of client/server
- Designed a brand new UI for the site and Integrated Bootstrap4 and ParticleJs into the site
- Handled problems/issues and make prompt solutions to resolve them
- Helped boost company's online presence & website traffic

Radio Fodder - University of Melbourne Student Radio, Web developer 2018.01 – 2018.08

- Project link http://www.radiofodder.com
- Redesigned and developed the site individually
- Integrated a new online radio system into the site

Chinese Students and Scholars Association (CSSA), Head of IT department 2016.09 – 2017.09

- Project link http://www.cssaunimelb.com
- Designed a brand new website for CSSA
- Developed a membership management system to store more than 5000+ members' information
- Manage and supported critical online information systems of CSSA

MelMel Consulting PTY LTD, Software Developer

2015.06 - 2017.01

- Project link:
 - o http://www.rejoiceworld.com.au
 - o http://www.melmel.com.au/service
- Revised programming and software development projects by updating code and working to improve functionality.
- Designed and deployed the wordpress website for customers

OTHER PROJECTS

ReactNative Project: https://github.com/COMP30022-18/BluePanda_Server
Unimods.com.au: https://github.com/cS2103AUG2017-T13-B2/main
NUS NextBus(Adobe XD): Mock-up Link
Wechat ChatBot: https://github.com/LinusMelb/WechatChatBot

LANGUAGE

Finglish — Fluent

LANGUAGE English – Fluent

Mandarin – Native

PERSONAL WEBSITE https://linusmelb.github.io/